module.exports = [
  {
    question: 'Who is also known as "Bubba"?', 
    a: 'Taylor',
    b: 'Tom',
    c: 'Troy',
    d: 'JoCo',
    answer: 'd'
  },
  {
    question: 'Which one of these nicknames is NOT owned by Billy?', 
    a: 'Wild Bill',
    b: 'The Human Tampon',
    c: 'Mr. Smooth',
    d: 'Galileo',
    answer: 'd'
  },
  {
    question: 'What is Haleyâ€™s nickname?', 
    a: 'Paley',
    b: 'Scarlett Fever',
    c: 'Irish Heat',
    d: 'None of the Above',
    answer: 'd'
  },
  {
    question: 'Who goes by the nickname "Mean Mug"?', 
    a: 'Molly',
    b: 'Dante',
    c: 'Tom',
    d: 'None of the Above',
    answer: 'a'
  },
  {
    question: 'Brady goes by which of the following WORK nicknames?', 
    a: 'Bizzle',
    b: 'B-Rad',
    c: 'Bray-quan',
    d: 'None of the Above',
    answer: 'c'
  },
  {
    question: 'Kellee was also known as which names?', 
    a: 'Kimberlee',
    b: 'Keezy',
    c: 'Baby',
    d: 'None of the Above',
    answer: 'a'
  },
  {
    question: 'Which of these is NOT a Turkish nickname for Mercan?', 
    a: 'Spaghetti',
    b: 'Naber',
    c: 'Patates',
    d: 'None of the Above',
    answer: 'd'
  },
  {
    question: 'What is Troy\'s nickname?', 
    a: 'Shooter McAcosta',
    b: 'Jackhammer Junglecat',
    c: 'The Big Pickle',
    d: 'Chanco',
    answer: 'b'
  },
  {
    question: 'What is Jeff\'s nickname?', 
    a: 'Latex Layton',
    b: 'Dr. Boozey',
    c: 'Yo Yo Mah',
    d: 'None of the Above',
    answer: 'b'
  },
  {
    question: 'Who has the childhood nickname Motts?', 
    a: 'BDF',
    b: 'Brandon',
    c: 'Molly',
    d: 'Devon',
    answer: 'c'
  },
];